cmcmarketsstockbroking.com.au 2011-09-20

# PRIVACY STATEMENT

                        PRIVACY STATEMENT
                      How we can help you                                                      Recordings or transcripts made by CMC Markets of your telephone
                      We welcome your comments. Should there be some way you feel              conversations may be destroyed under CMC Markets’ normal practice,
                      that we can improve our service, we’d like to know. Whether you are      which is to destroy them usually, but not necessarily, two calendar
                      making a suggestion, paying a compliment or making a complaint,          months after the date of the conversation.
                      your feedback is the key to improving our products and services.
                                                                                               CMC Markets’ Websites
                      For assistance call 1300 660 262 or you can email us your                - Statistical Information and Cookies
                      comments directly at clientservices@cmcmarkets.com.au                    We collect statistical information about visitors to our websites such as
                                                                                               the number of visitors, pages viewed, types of transactions conducted,
                                                                                               time online and documents downloaded. This information is used to
                                                                                               evaluate and improve the performance of our websites. Other than
                      This Privacy Statement explains how the CMC Markets Group                statistical information, we do not collect any information about you
                      (“CMC Markets”) collects, maintains, uses and discloses your             through our website unless you provide the information to us.
                      personal information. It also provides some detail about the rights
                      that custo-mers have in respect of their personal information. For       You should also be aware that we use cookies on our websites.
                      the purpose of this Privacy Statement, members of the CMC Markets        A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique
                      Group include CMC Markets Asia Pacific Pty Ltd (ABN 11 100 058           identification number or value that is sent to your browser from
                      213), CMC Markets Stockbroking Limited (ABN 69 081 002 851),             a website’s computer and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Each
                      CMC Markets Pty Ltd (ABN 75 100 058 106) and other related               website can send its own cookies to your browser if your browser
                      companies.                                                               allows it. However, to protect your privacy, your browser only allows
                                                                                               a website to access the cookies it has sent to your computer.
                      Personal Information
                      You provide CMC Markets with your personal information when              When cookies are used on our websites, they are used to collect the
                      you ask for information about CMC Markets’ products and services,        statistical information referred to above in addition to allowing you
                      when you access and use this and other CMC Markets websites              to access your account online. When you access your account on-line
                      and/or when you submit an application to open an account with            a cookie will be created which uniquely identifies your computer and
                      CMC Markets. When assessing an application, CMC Markets may              your username and password. This means that you do not have to re-
                      also collect information about you from publicly available sources       enter those details each time you want to access your account online.
                      such as company registers.
                                                                                               Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. If you do not
                      If you give us personal information about another person, you            wish to receive cookies, you may be able to change the settings of
                      represent that you are authorised to do so and agree to inform           your browser to refuse all cookies or to have your computer notify you
                      that person who we are, that we will use and disclose that information   each time a cookie is sent to it, and thereby give yourself the choice
                      for the relevant purposes set out below and that they can access the     whether to accept it or not. If you reject all cookies, you will be unable
                      information we hold about them.                                          to access your account online. You can also delete cookies from your
                                                                                               computer after they have been created.
                      CMC Markets maintains records of all transactions and activities on
                      accounts you have with CMC Markets, including details of contracts       Use of the Information by CMC Markets
                      traded and margin calls made. During the course of your relationship     The information requested in any application to open an account
                      with CMC Markets, we will also gather information about products         completed by customers is required to enable us to provide a service
                      and services provided to you.                                            to you. That information, together with the information collected and
                                                                                               maintained by CMC Markets during the course of our relationship
                      We are required by law to collect information to identify and verify     with you, is used to manage and administer the products and services
                      you. Your personal information will be treated strictly in accordance    provided to you and to keep you updated whilst you are a customer
                      with the National Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and   in relation to various matters including the contracts you have traded,
                      the ‘private sector amendments’ contained in the Privacy Amendment       your margin obligations, the funds in your account, and other activi-
                      (Private Sector) Act 2000 (Cth).                                         ties of CMC Markets.
                      Telephone Conversations                                                  We may also use your personal information to develop an under-
                      CMC Markets may record telephone conversations between you               standing of the products and services that you may be interested
                      and persons working for CMC Markets. Such recordings, or transcripts     in obtaining from CMC Markets and to market such products and
                      from such recordings, may be used to resolve any dispute between         services to you.
                      you and CMC Markets.
0110_PRIV_STATEMENT

CMC Markets may disclose your personal information to:                       from us notwithstanding registration at any time of your telephone
•	financial institutions and other similar organisations that it deals     number on the Do Not Call Register.
         with in the course of its corporate activities, or those that are
         nominated by you;                                                   Receiving commercial electronic messages
                                                                             By accessing this website you consent to us sending commercial
 •	external service providers and professional advisers (which may         electronic messages (including messages about our products and
         be located overseas) that provide services to us;                   services) to any electronic address which you provide or for which
                                                                             you are responsible. You warrant that you have authority, either as
  •	any organisation at your request or any persons acting on your         or on behalf of the electronic account holder, to provide this consent
         behalf, including your financial adviser, broker, solicitor or      and agree that until you withdraw your consent by providing written
         accountant;                                                         notice to us or using an unsubscribe facility in the message, we may
                                                                             continue to send commercial electronic messages to those addresses.
   •	regulatory and government bodies from time to time in Australia
         and other countries; and                                            Your Consent
                                                                             By accessing this website or by submitting an application to open an
    • CMC Markets plc and its associates.                                   account with CMC Markets, you consent to CMC Markets collecting,
                                                                             maintaining, using and disclosing personal information about you
     CMC Markets takes all reasonable steps to protect your personal         and provided by you or by another person as described above.
     information from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification
     or disclosure.                                                          Amendments to this Privacy Statement
                                                                             CMC Markets may make changes to this Privacy Statement from
     What are your rights?                                                   time to time for any reason. This Privacy Statement is dated
     You need not give us any of the personal information requested          30 October 2009.
     by CMC Markets. However, without that information CMC Markets
     will not be able to open an account for you where the information
     is requested in an application form, or to provide you with any other
     services, information or assistance you have sought.
     Should you have any questions or complaint about your privacy
     please contact us. If a complaint is not resolved by CMC Markets
     to your satisfaction, you may complain to the Privacy Commissioner.
     Access to Information by Customers
     Customers can gain access to any information CMC Markets holds
     about them by calling +1300 660 262 or emailing
     clientservices@cmcmarkets.com.au. We will process your request
     usually within 14 days. If your request is complex, more time may
     be needed in which case we will advise you of the extra time required.
     There is no fee for requesting access to your information, although
     CMC Markets may charge you the reasonable cost of processing your
     request.
     In some circumstances the law may allow CMC Markets to deny you
     access. In such a case we will explain to you the reason for refusing
     access.
     Correction of Information
     We ask that you promptly notify us of any changes to the personal
     information that CMC Markets holds about you. This ensures that
     your personal information is up to date and enables us to keep you
     informed of the continuing circumstances of your account, your
     margin obligations and your trading activities.
     You may ask us at any time to correct personal information held by
     CMC Markets about you, and which you believe is inaccurate. Should
     we disagree with you as to the accuracy of the information, you may
     request that we attach a statement to that information noting that you
     consider it inaccurate or incomplete.
     Do Not Call Register
     Unless you ask us by calling +1300 660 262 not to contact you about
     products or services and not to disclose your information to others for
     that purpose, by accessing this website you consent to us contacting
     you by telephone while you hold any product or receive any services
